<resources>
    <!-- App main structure -->
    <string name="app_name">Visit New Zealand</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="sights">Sights</string>
    <string name="sleep">Sleep</string>
    <string name="eat">Eat</string>

    <!--All Items standards -->
    <string name="place_title">Place</string>
    <string name="contact_title">Contact</string>
    <string name="address_title">Address</string>


    <string-array name="spinner_cities">
        <item>Auckland</item>
        <item>Wellington</item>
        <item>Christchurch</item>
        <item>Hamilton</item>
        <item>Tauranga</item>
        <item>Napier-Hastings</item>
        <item>Dunedin</item>
        <item>Palmerston North</item>
        <item>Nelson</item>
        <item>Rotorua</item>
        <item>Whangarei</item>
        <item>New Plymouth</item>
        <item>Invercargill</item>
        <item>Whanganui</item>
        <item>Gisborne</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Label About -->
    <string name="city">City</string>
    <string name="population">Population</string>
    <string name="airports">Airport</string>
    <string name="transports">Transports</string>
    <string name="about_city">About the city</string>

    <!-- Auckland -->
    <string name="template_city">Auckland</string>
    <string name="template_population">1,534,700</string>
    <string name="template_airports">Auckland Airport</string>
    <string name="template_transports">Ferry, train, flight and bus</string>
    <string name="template_about_city">Auckland (/ˈɔːklənd/ AWK-lənd) is a city in New Zealand\'s North Island. Auckland is the largest urban area in the country, with an urban population of around 1,534,700.[4] It is located in the Auckland Region—the area governed by Auckland Council—which includes outlying rural areas and the islands of the Hauraki Gulf, resulting in a total population of 1,657,200. A diverse and multicultural city, Auckland is home to the largest Polynesian population in the world. The Māori-language name for Auckland is Tāmaki or Tāmaki-makau-rau, meaning "Tāmaki with a hundred lovers", in reference to the desirability of its fertile land at the hub of waterways in all directions. It has also been called Ākarana, a transliteration of the English name.
        The Auckland urban area (as defined by Statistics New Zealand) ranges to Waiwera in the north, Kumeu in the northwest, and Runciman in the south. Auckland lies between the Hauraki Gulf of the Pacific Ocean to the east, the low Hunua Ranges to the south-east, the Manukau Harbour to the south-west, and the Waitakere Ranges and smaller ranges to the west and north-west. The surrounding hills are covered in rainforest and the landscape is dotted with dozens of dormant volcanic cones. The central part of the urban area occupies a narrow isthmus between the Manukau Harbour on the Tasman Sea and the Waitematā Harbour on the Pacific Ocean. Auckland is one of the few cities in the world to have a harbour on each of two separate major bodies of water.</string>

    <!-- Fragment Sights Top 10 -->
    <string name="sight1">SkyTower</string>
    <string name="sight2">Waitakere Ranges</string>
    <string name="sight3">Viaduct Harbour</string>
    <string name="sight4">One Tree Hill (Maungakiekie)</string>
    <string name="sight5">North Head Historic Reserve</string>
    <string name="sight6">Ponsonby</string>
    <string name="sight7">Parnell</string>
    <string name="sight8">Howick Historical Village</string>
    <string name="sight9">Queen Street</string>
    <string name="sight10">Ferry Building</string>

    <string name="sight1phone">09-363 6000</string>
    <string name="sight2phone">9 365 9918</string>
    <string name="sight3phone">9 365 9918</string>
    <string name="sight4phone">09-600 1545</string>
    <string name="sight5phone">09-362 0655</string>
    <string name="sight6phone">09-377 7780</string>
    <string name="sight7phone">09-303 0150</string>
    <string name="sight8phone">09-379 5656</string>
    <string name="sight9phone">09-379 5151</string>
    <string name="sight10phone">09-379 5353</string>

    <string name="sight1Address">Corner Victoria and Federal Sts, Auckland Central, Auckland 1010, New Zealand</string>
    <string name="sight2Address">Arataki Visitor Centre | 300 Scenic Drive, Titirangi, Auckland Central, Auckland 0604, New Zealand</string>
    <string name="sight3Address">Viaduct Harbour Ave, Auckland Central, Auckland 1010, New Zealand</string>
    <string name="sight4Address">670 Manukau Road | Epsom, Auckland Central, Auckland 1023, New Zealand</string>
    <string name="sight5Address">Takarunga Rd. | Devonport, Auckland Central, Auckland, New Zealand</string>
    <string name="sight6Address">Auckland Central, Auckland, New Zealand</string>
    <string name="sight7Address">Parnell Road, Auckland Central, Auckland 1052, New Zealand</string>
    <string name="sight8Address">Bells Road | Lloyd Elsmore Park, Howick, Auckland Central, Auckland, New Zealand</string>
    <string name="sight9Address">Auckland Central, Auckland, New Zealand</string>
    <string name="sight10Address">Ferry Building 99 Quay Street, Auckland Central, Auckland 1010, New Zealand</string>

    <string name="sight1description">Auckland\'s Sky Tower is the tallest structure in the Southern Hemisphere, this tower is more than 300 metres high. Offering stunning views, along with award winning restaurants, a gift shop and an opportunity to push your limits by walking the outside of the viewing platforms, or by jumping off from 192 metres above Auckland\'s CBD.</string>
    <string name="sight2description">This scenic drive takes you past bush scenery, to observation points for spectacular views and to gorgeous beaches.</string>
    <string name="sight3description">Visit the center of Auckland sailing and the place for the finest restaurants, bars, and luxury apartments.</string>

    <string name="sights_location_1">-36.8484437,174.7600023,17z</string>
    <string name="sights_location_2">-37.0136954,174.5542605,11z</string>
    <string name="sights_location_3">-36.8429654,174.7559422,16z</string>
    <string name="sights_location_4">-36.899982,174.7745785,15z</string>
    <string name="sights_location_5">-36.8270751,174.8096291,17z</string>
    <string name="sights_location_6">-36.8505695,174.7304198,15z</string>
    <string name="sights_location_7">-36.8556312,174.770044,14z</string>
    <string name="sights_location_8">-36.9074857,174.9005203,17z</string>
    <string name="sights_location_9">-36.8508956,174.7623284,17z</string>
    <string name="sights_location_10">-36.8429846,174.7647521,17z</string>

    <!-- Fragment Sleep Categories -->
    <string name="accommodation1">Bed &amp; Breakfast</string>
    <string name="accommodation2">Backpacker Hostel</string>
    <string name="accommodation3">Boutique Hotel</string>
    <string name="accommodation4">Guest House </string>
    <string name="accommodation5">Hotel </string>
    <string name="accommodation6">Lodge </string>
    <string name="accommodation7">Private Home </string>
    <string name="accommodation8">Resort </string>
    <string name="accommodation9">Self-Catering </string>

    <string name="accommodation_descr_1">A Bed and Breakfast (B&amp;B) is a private home in which guests can be accommodated at night in private bedrooms (which may or may not have private bathrooms).
        The owner or manager lives in the house or on the property. The public areas of the house, such as kitchen and lounge have either limited access for guests, or are shared with the host family to some degree.
        The business may be run as a secondary occupation.
        Breakfast is included in the price (generally either continental or full-English). Other meals may be available by arrangement..</string>

    <string name="accommodation_descr_2">A hostel (or backpacker) establishment is aimed at the budget traveller and generally attracts a younger clientele.
        Bedrooms are in a dormitory style (shared) and bathrooms are shared, although private bedrooms may be available.
        Light meals may be available in addition to the room rate.</string>

    <string name="accommodation_descr_3">A boutique hotel is a 5 star establishment providing all the features and facilities of a normal hotel, in a unique and exclusive style.
        These properties are generally small, feature top class service and are marketed to the affluent.</string>

    <string name="accommodation_descr_4">A guesthouse is generally a private home which has been converted for the dedicated and exclusive use of guest accommodation.
    The public areas of the establishment are for the exclusive use of the guests. The owner or manager either lives off-site, or in an entirely separate area within the property.
    A Guesthouse offers a wider range of services than a B&amp;B, and usually caters for all meals.</string>

    <string name="accommodation_descr_5">A hotel is generally the largest of all accommodation types.
    There is typically a common reception area, and rooms generally open directly onto a hallway.
    The on-site restaurant and other facilities are more accessible to the public than the other accommodation types.
    A wide range of guest services is available, such as room service.
    Hotels are often members of larger hotel groups, and a similar accommodation experience may be available in different establishments within the group.
    </string>

    <string name="accommodation_descr_6">A lodge is an accommodation facility which is located and designed to optimize the feeling of being closely in touch with nature.
    The building style should feature natural materials and colouring such as wood, stone and thatch.
    An outdoor experience should be offered at the lodge, such as guided walks, game drives etc.
    </string>
    <string name="accommodation_descr_7">A private home not dedicated for full time occupation of guests, but is a private house or apartment which is temporarily available for rental, often during peak tourism seasons.
    </string>
    <string name="accommodation_descr_8">A spread out collection of single or double story accommodation units.
    Similar to a hotel in that it offers a wide range of facilities.
    Units may be rented and available on time-share.
    A camping area may be included in the resort.
    </string>
    <string name="accommodation_descr_9">A self catering establishment may be primarily one of the other accommodation types, but also offers dedicated self catering facilities.
    The unit should feature a fully equipped kitchen to cater for the maximum people to be accommodated (including fridge, stove, cutlery, crockery, cooking utensils, cleaning equipment).
    The kitchen should be for the exclusive use of the guests, and not shared.
    </string>

    <!-- Fragment Flatmates -->
    <string name="flatmate1">New Windsor, 5 bedrooms</string>
    <string name="flatmate2">Royal Oak, 5 bedrooms</string>
    <string name="flatmate3">Albany, 5 bedrooms</string>
    <string name="flatmate4">Grafton, 5 bedrooms</string>
    <string name="flatmate5">Sandringham, 2 bedrooms</string>
    <string name="flatmate6">Flat Bush, 4 bedrooms</string>
    <string name="flatmate7">Conifer Grove, 4 bedrooms</string>

    <string name="flatmate1phone">021 1901614</string>
    <string name="flatmate2phone">021 2901614</string>
    <string name="flatmate3phone">021 3901614</string>
    <string name="flatmate4phone">021 4901614</string>
    <string name="flatmate5phone">021 5901614</string>
    <string name="flatmate6phone">021 6901614</string>
    <string name="flatmate7phone">021 7901614</string>

    <string name="flatmate1Address">New Windsor - Auckland City - Auckland</string>
    <string name="flatmate2Address">Royal Oak - Auckland City - Auckland</string>
    <string name="flatmate3Address">Albany - North Shore City - Auckland</string>
    <string name="flatmate4Address">Grafton - Auckland City - Auckland</string>
    <string name="flatmate5Address">Sandringham - Auckland City - Auckland</string>
    <string name="flatmate6Address">Flat Bush - Manukau City - Auckland</string>
    <string name="flatmate7Address">Conifer Grove - Papakura - Auckland</string>

    <string name="flatmate1Description">5 bedroom house with 2 bathrooms. 5 Bedroom, two story flat with 2 Bathrooms.
        Looking for one flat mate to fill in my space
        The flat is a 10min walk away from the train station and bus stop is right around the corner, it\'s around 30min transport to the CBD and a 10min drive with your own vehicle. Their is off road parking and a massive back yard.
        $147.50 p/w
        Bond is two weeks rent
        Wifi is $20 a month
        water is around $15-$17 a month
        Power is $40 a month
        Smokers OK, no pets</string>

    <string name="flatmate2Description">5 bedroom house with 2 bathrooms.
        Available from 28th January
        5 bedroom house with 2 bathrooms.
        Trade Me Advertisement – 873 Manukau Road, Royal Oak
        Rent per week: $185 (plus $30 bills)
        Available from: 28th January 2018
        Location: Royal Oak
        Number of existing flatmates: 4
        Property Type: House
        Bedrooms: 5
        Bathrooms: 2
        Pets: No pets
        Smokers: Outside
        Details:
        Large 5 bedroom, 2 bathroom 2 storey house.
        Looking for a Male or Female to come join our flat (currently 2 guys &amp; 2 girls)
        The available room have just been constructed and is fully insulated and located on the ground floor.
        The property is located just down from Royal Oak roundabout and a convenient bus stop located just metres from the property
        Smokers OK, no pets</string>

    <string name="flatmate3Description">5 bedroom house with 3 bathrooms.
        One double bedroom will be available in a modern 5 bedroom house. The house is located in a very quiet and safe street, easy access to the motorway in Fairview Heights.
        The room is on the 1st floor which gets sunlight most of the day. Fully furnished with a queen size bed, bedside table, chair, study desk. Also comes with big wardrobe in the bedroom. You will have your own toilet and shower located just outside the room.
        House has 3 lounges (1 upstairs, 2downstairs)
        Kitchen and laundry downstairs.
        Rent includes power, gas, water and unlimited internet.
        We are a couple in our 20s, easy going. All of us are in our 20s working full time and are quite international. Also, we have a 10 years old rough collie, and 1 and half-year-old White Shepherd. They would stay inside the house with us.
        We are looking for a tidy, and mature person who is a dog lover to move in with us. smoker is ok but only outside.
        2 weeks bond and one week rent in advance.
        You can give me call or message any time for viewing
        Millie 02108276339
        Smokers OK, no pets</string>

    <string name="flatmate4Description">5 bedroom house with 5 bathrooms.
        This is a quality accomodation on offer.The villa is tucked away down a no exit street but just a stroll away from Newmarket and Auckland Hospital.
        It is bright and modern with open plan living and a deck overlooking the garden through french doors
        There is a fully equipped kitchen and laundry and a comfortable lounge for catching up with your flatmates and friends.
        The bedroom is fully furnished with a queen bed, ample wardrobe and drawer space bar fridge and microwave and looks out onto the sunny garden.
        Ensuite shower ,vanity, toilet
        No couples,pets or smokers.
        No pets or smokers.</string>

    <string name="flatmate5Description">	2 bedroom unit with 1 bathroom.
        Looking for short term flattie
        1 furnished single bedroom to rent in Sandringham (Oxton Road). Rent is $200 plus bills or $230 inc bills. Will need 1 week for bond and week upon moving in plus sign a flatmate agreement.
        Heaps of storage in the garage.
        No pets or smokers.</string>

    <string name="flatmate6Description">	4 bedroom house with 3 bathrooms.
        Near new quality 4 bedrooms and 3 bathrooms, 3 living areas, 2 kitchens house looking for a clean and tidy working flatmate. The house is located in a new Ormiston area which is next to all amenties. Bus stop just outside the road, Mcdonalds and Pak n Save etc. Facing a amazing park views. Upmarket finishes and chattels HRV systems, air-conditioning and underfloor heating. Prefered working female, however quite male could be considerable. Couples are welcome.
        The room for rent is a double bedroom with HRV ventilation system, big window and quite. It comes with a near new queen bed and a side table.
        We are a happy couple with a 2 years happy boy. Come and meet us and have a look around. You won\'t regret it. ^o^
        **Please leave a message on my phone and I will get back to you very soon. Thanks. **
        No pets or smokers.</string>

    <string name="flatmate7Description">4 bedroom house with 2 bathrooms.
        Downstaris bedroom available to Rent.
        Rent includes Power, Water, Wifi and basic kitchen items.
        4 Bedroom large house with 2 lounges.
        Rented room is downstaris with Toilet/vanity next to it - other bedrooms all upstaris and shower and another toilet, I have ensuite so pretty much your own bathroom.
        Situated at end of a culdesac - very safe area.
        1 TV has Sky and other has Google Cast for Netflix etc
        Room has Furniture and bedding if you need.No pets.</string>

    <string name="flatmate_location_1">-36.9040558,174.7046399,15z</string>
    <string name="flatmate_location_2">-36.9105399,174.7624982,15z</string>
    <string name="flatmate_location_3">-36.7345931,174.6816716,14z</string>
    <string name="flatmate_location_4">-36.8608996,174.7575403,15z</string>
    <string name="flatmate_location_5">-36.8879967,174.7185396,14z</string>
    <string name="flatmate_location_6">-36.9736861,174.8963783,13z</string>
    <string name="flatmate_location_7">-37.0454281,174.9038104,15z</string>

    <!-- Fragment FoodsAndDrinks -->
    <string name="restaurant1">POKPOK Thai Restaurant &amp; Bar</string>
    <string name="restaurant2">Katsura Japanese Restaurant</string>
    <string name="restaurant3">Coco\'s Cantina</string>
    <string name="restaurant4">Gemmayze Street</string>
    <string name="restaurant5">Le Garde Manger</string>
    <string name="restaurant6">Rasoi Vegetarian Restaurant</string>
    <string name="restaurant7">Il Mee Restaurant</string>
    <string name="restaurant8">Kura Japanese Restaurant</string>
    <string name="restaurant9">Tanuki\'s Cave</string>
    <string name="restaurant10">Tanuki Japanese Restaurant</string>
    <string name="restaurant11">Odettes Eatery</string>

    <string name="restaurant1phone">09-963 9987</string>
    <string name="restaurant2phone">09-366 3000</string>
    <string name="restaurant3phone">09-300 7582</string>
    <string name="restaurant4phone">09-600 1545</string>
    <string name="restaurant5phone">09-362 0655</string>
    <string name="restaurant6phone">09-377 7780</string>
    <string name="restaurant7phone">09-303 0150</string>
    <string name="restaurant8phone">09-379 5656</string>
    <string name="restaurant9phone">09-379 5151</string>
    <string name="restaurant10phone">09-379 5353</string>
    <string name="restaurant11phone">09-309 0304</string>

    <string name="restaurant1Address">261 Karangahape Rd</string>
    <string name="restaurant2Address">71 Mayoral Dr</string>
    <string name="restaurant3Address">376 Karangahape Rd</string>
    <string name="restaurant4Address">Shop 16, St Kevin\'s Arcade, 183 Karangahape Rd</string>
    <string name="restaurant5Address">466 Queen Street</string>
    <string name="restaurant6Address">211 Karangahape Rd</string>
    <string name="restaurant7Address">480 Queen St</string>
    <string name="restaurant8Address">315B Queen St</string>
    <string name="restaurant9Address">319 Queen St</string>
    <string name="restaurant10Address">319 Queen St</string>
    <string name="restaurant11Address">90 Wellesley St W</string>

    <string name="restaurant1Description">Thai Restaurant</string>
    <string name="restaurant2Description">Contemporary setup at the Grand Millennium Auckland featuring tableside teppanyaki chefs &amp; sushi.</string>
    <string name="restaurant3Description">Great cocktails · Cosy · Casual</string>
    <string name="restaurant4Description">Lebanese Restaurant</string>
    <string name="restaurant5Description">Relaxed &amp; homey French restaurant offering a range of crêpes, traditional mains &amp; wine.</string>
    <string name="restaurant6Description">Unfussy, counter-serve outpost featuring a menu of vegetarian Indian dishes, sweets &amp; snacks.</string>
    <string name="restaurant7Description">Cosy · Casual · Good for kids</string>
    <string name="restaurant8Description">Sushi Restaurant</string>
    <string name="restaurant9Description">Yakitori Restaurant</string>
    <string name="restaurant10Description">Japanese Restaurant</string>
    <string name="restaurant11Description">Mediterranean Restaurant</string>

    <string name="restaurant_location_1">-36.856566, 174.758455</string>
    <string name="restaurant_location_2">-36.851861, 174.760729</string>
    <string name="restaurant_location_3">-36.857870, 174.756683</string>
    <string name="restaurant_location_4">-36.857228, 174.760122</string>
    <string name="restaurant_location_5">-36.855597, 174.762493</string>
    <string name="restaurant_location_6">-36.857421, 174.759596</string>
    <string name="restaurant_location_7">-36.855771, 174.762290</string>
    <string name="restaurant_location_8">-36.853287, 174.763031</string>
    <string name="restaurant_location_9">-36.853335, 174.763200</string>
    <string name="restaurant_location_10">-36.853377, 174.763170</string>
    <string name="restaurant_location_11">-36.849571, 174.758403</string>

    <!-- Others -->
    <string name="tourist_information">Tourist Information</string>
    <string name="go">Go</string>
</resources>

